{
    "subject": "Pieter_Verhoeff",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Mates__film_",
    "human_readable": "Pieter Verhoeff created the film Mates.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9155292510986328,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Pieter Verhoeff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7946295738220215,
            "question": "Is Pieter Verhoeff known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5648326277732849,
            "question": "Who directed the film Mates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5048431158065796,
            "question": "Can you name any other films directed by Pieter Verhoeff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.481751024723053,
            "question": "When was the film Mates released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4446442127227783,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Mates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3862471282482147,
            "question": "Where was the film Mates filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36719679832458496,
            "question": "Who are the main actors in the film Mates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3537241518497467,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the reception of the film Mates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32826754450798035,
            "question": "What genre is the film Mates likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pieter Verhoeff created the film Mates.",
            "html": "yago_16307_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the reception of the film Mates?",
            "html": "yago_16307_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main actors in the film Mates?",
            "html": "yago_16307_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film Mates filmed?",
            "html": "yago_16307_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_16307_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Pieter Verhoeff created the film Mates.\" Specifically, both `73.txt` and `59.txt` mention Pieter Verhoeff as the director of the film Mates."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}